Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Administrative Files, 1954-1961
  - Subseries 1: Contributors -- Manuscripts and Correspondence
    - Cassity, Turner SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Cassity, Turner (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Casto, Robert (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Ce-Ch, Ceravole, Joseph Cesari, Isotta Chakravarty, Amiya Chamberlin, Myrtle Chambers, Willard E. Chametzky, Anne Chandler, David Chapin, Katherine Garrison SEE Biddle, Katherine Chapman, Asher Chappelli, ? (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Ch, Chase, Gilbert Chase, Kathleen Chase, Richard Chatterji, U.N. (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Ch, Chen, Paul S. Chhatre, U.K. Chickering, H.D. Chigounis, Evans C. Chipurnoi, Irene Christiansen, Mary Chrysantha, Sister M. Church, Margaret Churchill, Josephine Chute, Robert M. (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Ciardi, John SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Ciardi, John (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Ciardi, John (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Clad, Jean Davies (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Clark, David Ridgley (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Clark, John W. (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Cl, Clark, Laurence Clarke, Hilary Chatterbuck, M. Kay Clayborne, Mary M. Clayton, Charles C. Clements, Walter Clifton, C. Sterling Cloud, Jess Clough, Wilson (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Clower, Jean SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Clower, Jean (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Co, Coakley, William Leo Coates, La Priel Coatsworth, Elizabeth Cobb, Noel Cockerill, Donald J. (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Co, Code, Grant Codner, Ben J. Cogswell, Fred Cohen, Joseph (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Thomas (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Coleman, Elliott SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Coleman, Elliott (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Coleman, Elliott (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Co, Collie, Michael Collins, Ben Collins, David M. Collins, H.P. Colt, Byron (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Colum, Padraic (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Co, Colvin, Frances Conley, Ann Conley, Ruth Conn, Stewart Connell, Geoffrey Connor, Tony (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Co, Conquest, Robert Constant, Nickas Constantinoff, R.P. Converse, Joanne Cook, Albert Coolidge, John S. Coombs, Donald Coombs, Patricia (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Co, Cooper, George William Cooper, Jane Cooper, Robert (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Copley, Frank SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Co, Copping, Robert Corey, Ruth Lechlitner (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Corman, Cid (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Corman, Cid (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Co, Corrington, John William Cory, Daniel Cotter, James F. Cotterill, Iris Jean Coulette, Henri Court, Artelia Bowne Cousens, Mildred Coutts-Smith, Kenneth (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Cowley, Malcolm (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Cox, C.B. (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Coxe, Louis SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Coxe, Louis SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Coxe, Louis SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Coxe, Louis (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Coxe, Louis (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Crage, William D. (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Craig, Alexander SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Craig, Alexander (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Crawford, Betty (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Crawford, Jack (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Creekmore, Hubert (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Creeley, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Creeley, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Creeley, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Creeley, Robert (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Creeley, Robert (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Creeley, Robert (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Cr, Crenner, James T. Crescent, Helen (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Crews, Judson (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Cr-Cu, Crome, Nicholas L.M. Crowley, J.V. Crown, Rachel Cudahy, W. Culbertson, Ernest Howard (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Cummings, E.E. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Cu, Cunard, Nancy Cunningham, James V. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Cu, Curnow, Allen Cursons, Aline C. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Cutler, Bruce SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Cutler, Bruce (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Dahlberg, Edward SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Daiches, David (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Da, Dalton, Dorothy Dalton, Sheila M. (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Dalven, Rae SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Dalven, Rae (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Dana, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Daniels, Guy (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Danner, Margaret (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Da, Dannette, J. D'Arcos, Joaquim Paco D'Artois, Robert Darrow, Jay Das, Jamini Kanta Das, Jibananonda Datta, Sudhindranath (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Davie, Donald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Da, Davies, Ada Davis, Betty (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Davis, Catherine (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Da, Davis, H.L. Davison, Peter H. Day, Lena hall (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - De, Debee, Rajlukshmee DeBoe, Opal Decavalles, Andonis SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - De, deFord, Miriam Allen DeHirsch, Storm (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - DeJong, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - DeJong, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - DeJong, David (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - Delahunt, John (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - De, De la Mare, Walter Deming, Barbara Demovsky, Ronald (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Denney, Reuel SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Denney, Reuel SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Denney, Reuel SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Denney, Reuel (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Denzer, Peter W. (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Derwood, Gene (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Deutsch, Babette (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Deutsch, Babette SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Deutsch, Babette SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Deutsch, Babette (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Deutsch, Babette (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Devanesen, Chandran (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Dickey, James, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Dickey, James, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Dickey, James, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Dickey, James, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Dickey, James, prose SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Dickey, James, prose SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Dickey, James, correspondence (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Dickey, James, correspondence (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Dickey, James, correspondence (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - Dickey, William SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Dickey, William SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - Dietz, Florence A. (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Dillon, George SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Dillon, George (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - Dillon, George (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - Di-Do, Dixon, Alan Doherty, Kevin F. Donaldson, Theodore (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Donnelly, Dorothy SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Donnelly, Dorothy SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Donnelly, Dorothy SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Donnelly, Dorothy (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Donoghue, Denis SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Donoghue, Denis (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Do, Donohue, H.E.F. Donovan, Laurence Doob, Eveline Bates (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Doolittle, Hilda SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Dory, Edward (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Doughty, LeGarde S. (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Do-Dr, Dowden, George Doyle, Charles Drake, Carol Christopher Drake, Leah Bodine (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Dr-Du, Drubeck, Pearl B. Drury, Finvola Dudek, Louis Dudson, Margery F. Duesing, C.J. Duffy, William (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Dugan, Alan SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Dugan, Alan (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Du, Dulac, Margarita Duncan, Harry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Duncan, Robert, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Duncan, Robert, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Duncan, Robert, poetry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Duncan, Robert, poetry (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Duncan, Robert, prose SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Duncan, Robert, prose SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Duncan, Robert, correspondence (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Duncan, Robert, correspondence (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Duncan, Robert, correspondence (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Du-Dy SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Dunetz, Lora Dunlop, Betty Dunn, Stephen Dysinger, Robert E. (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Eaddy, Carroll M. (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Eaton, Charles Edward (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Eaton, Charles Edward (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Eaton, Walter H. (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Eberhart, Richard SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - Eberhart, Richard SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - Eberhart, Richard SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - Eberhart, Richard (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Eberhart, Richard (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Eberhart, Richard (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Eberhart, Richard (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Eberhart, Richard (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Eckman, Frederick SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Eckman, Frederick (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Ec-Ed, Eckrich, Catherine Edelstein, J. M. Edmonds, Mary (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Ed-Ei, Edwards, John SEE ALSO OVERSIZE Eigner, L. Eisen, Jeffrey (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Eliot, T.S. (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - El, Elliott, George P. Ellison, Liane (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - El, Ellman, Richard Elman, Richard (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Elmslie, Kenward SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Elton, William (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - El-Em SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Ely, Gladys Emrich, Robert (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Engels, John D. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Engels, John D. (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Engle, Paul SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Engle, Paul (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - English, Maurice SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - En, Enrico, Harold Enright, D. J. Enscoe, Gerald Ensminger, Arline Ensslin, Walter Enzensberger, Hans Magnus (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Ep-Er, Epple, William S. Erba, Luciano (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Es-Ev, Esler, Richard Curry Esselin, Joe Esty, Jane Etter, David Pearson Evans, Arthur R. Evans, Patrick (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Everson, Landis (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Everson, Ronald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Everson, Ronald (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Ev-Ez SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Everwine, Peter Ezekiel, Nissim (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Fa, Facos, James Fairfax, John (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Fandel, John (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Fa-Fe, Farber, Norma Fargion, Marisa Farina, Richard Farkas, Zoltan L. Feeney, Coleman Feldman, Anne (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Feldman, Irving (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Fe, Feldzamen, A.N. Felstiner, John Fergusson, Francis (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Ferril, Thomas Hornsby (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Fe, Ferrini, Vincent Ferry, David Fey, Isabella (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Fiedler, Leslie SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Fiedler, Leslie (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Fiedler, Leslie (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Fi SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Field, Edward Fields, Ann Figel-Hartman, D. Fink, Abby (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Finkel, Donald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Finkel, Donald (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Fi, Finnegan, Dick Fireside, Harvey Fisher, Virginia (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Fitts, Dudley SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Fitts, Dudley SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Fitts, Dudley (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Fi, Fitzell, Lincoln Fitzgerald, Edward James (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Fitzgerald, Gerald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Fi-Fj, Fitzsimmons, Thomas Fjilde, Rolf (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Fl, Flaccus, Kimball Fleischer, Roy Fleisher, Frederic (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Fleming, Harold (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Fleming, Harold SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Fletcher, John Gould (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Fl, Flint, Robert Flynn, John (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Fo, Fogel, Ruby Folsom, Franklin Ford, Gena Ford, Kenneth H. Ford, R.A.D. Forgotson, E.S. Forslund, David Foster, Richard Fox, I.A. (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1956-57 (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1956-57 (Box 113, Folder 27)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1958-61 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1958-61 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1958-61 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, correspondence, 1958-61 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Francis, Robert (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Fr, Frank, Bernhard Frank, Larry Frank, R. Berezo Frankenberg, Lloyd (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Fraser, G.S. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Fr, Fraser, Kathleen Freed, Shelley J. Freedman, Michele Freeman, Arthur (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Fr, Freeman, C. Freeman, Collie M. Freeman, Joseph Fremantle, Richard (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Frezza, Luciana (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Friar, Kimon SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Friar, Kimon (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Friar, Kimon (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Friar, Kimon (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Fr, Frias, Carlos Virgilio Frias, George Fried, Michael M. Friedenberg, Daniel M. Friedman, Florence Louie Friedman, John B. Friedmann, Anthony (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Friedrich, Gerhard (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Friend, Robert (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Friend, Robert (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Fr, Friston, Allen Frost, Richard (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Frost, Robert (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Frost, Robert (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Frumkin, Gene SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Frye, Burton, and Virginia Chapin Frye (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Frye, Burton, and Virginia Chapin Frye (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Fujitomi, Yasudo (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Fuller, John (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Fu, Fuller, Roy Furlong, Waltrina Fussell, Edwin (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Ga, Gale, Vi Galkain, Carl (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Galler, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - Galler, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Galler, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Galler, David (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Ga, Galvin, Patrick Ganesh, V. Gante, Pablo C. de Gardener, William Gardien, Kent Gardner, E.F. (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Gardner, Isabella (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Gardner, Isabella (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Ga, Gardner, Philip Garrett, Charlotte Garrett, George (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Garrigue, Jean SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Garrigue, Jean SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Garrigue, Jean SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Garrigue, Jean (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Garrigue, Jean (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Ga-Ge, Garvey, John Gaulkin, Charles Gause, Emerson Gee, Kenneth Geer, Helen R. (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Geiger, Don (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Geiger, Don (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Ge, Gemmell, Jean Genders, Ann N.W. George, Richard A. Gerrard, Michael Gershon, Karen (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Gh, Ghose, Zulfikar Ghosh, Kamal Krishna (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Gibbs, Barbara SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Gibbs, Barbara SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Gibbs, Barbara (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Gi, Gibson, Morgan Gibson, Victoria Gibson, Walker (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - Gi, Gifford, Adam Gifford, Henry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Gi, Gilbert, Jack Gilbert, Sister Mary Gildart, Robert Gilfond, Henry Gill, John J. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Gi, Gillett, Myrtle Mann Gillikin, Dure Jo Gillon, Adam Gilman, Frederic D. (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Ginsberg, Louis (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Gi, Giorno, John Giovanni, Norman Thomas di Giraudier, Antonio Giuliani, Alfredo (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Gl, Gladish, David Glaze, Andrew Gleason, Madeline Gleeson, Patrick Shannon Glen, Emilie Glixon, Niel Gloege, Randall (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Go, Goacher, Denis Gogarty, Oliver St. John Gokak, V.K. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE Gold, Hubert Goldberg, Jonathan Goldman, Mark I. Goldman, Michael (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Golffing, Francis SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Golffing, Francis (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Golffing, Francis (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Go, Goll, Ivan Gomringer, Eugene Gonzalez, Alberto Goodell, Lawrence (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Goodman, Paul SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Goodman, Paul SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Goodman, Paul SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Goodman, Paul (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Goodman, Paul (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Go, Goodreau, William Gopalan, G.R. Gordon, Ambrose Gordon, Don Gordon-Smith, Bruce (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Go-Gr, Gorman, Paul Gosling, Ray Gottheimer, Stanley Govig, Valerie Graham, W.S. Gramm, Edith Grant, James Russell (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Graves, Robert (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Gr, Graybeal, Marie Green, Amelia Green, Ernest S. Green, Philip Greenberg, Batyah Greenberg, Eliezer Greene, Herbert Greene, Jesse Laurance (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Gr, Greer, Scott Greet, Anne H. (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Gregor, Arthur SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Gregor, Arthur SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Gregor, Arthur (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Gregor, Arthur (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Gregor, Arthur (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Gregory, Frater (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Gregory, Horace SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - Gregory, Horace (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - Gregory, Horace (Box 116, Folder 30)
    - Gresser, Seymour (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Gr, Gricourt, Solange Grieg, Michael Griffin, Howard (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Gr, Grilikhes, Alexandra Gronowicz, Antoni Gronquist, Opal Gross, Harvey Gross, Joan Scott (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Grossman, Allen (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Gr, Grucci, Joe Grundy, T.R. (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Guenther, Charles SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Guenther, Charles (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Guenther, Charles (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Guenther, Charles (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Guenther, Charles (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Guest, Barbara (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Gulick, Alida Carey (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Gunn, Thom SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Gunn, Thom SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Gunn, Thom SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Gunn, Thom SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Gunn, Thom (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Gunn, Thom (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Gu, Guri, Hayim Guss, Jack R. Gustafson, Ralph Guthrie, Ramon (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Ha, Haag, John Haar, Franklin Haber, Tom Burns (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Ha SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Haiduke, Robert Haines, John Haislip, John Haldeman, Charles Halder, Ras Mohun Hale, Idolene Hoofer Hale, Nancy Hale, Oliver (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Halkin, Simon (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Halkin, Simon (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Ha, Hall, Ananda Benjamin Hall, Carol (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Hall, Donald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Hall, Donald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Hall, James B. (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Hall, James B. (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Ha, Hall, Kay DeBard Halliburton, D.G. Halpern, Martin Hambly, Charles H. (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Hamburger, Michael SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Hamburger, Michael (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Ha, Hamilton, Horace E. Hamm, Rose Hammer, Jeanne-Ruth (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Ha, Hammer, Louis Z. Hammond, Geraldine Hammond, Mac Hampton, Christopher Hanen, Peter Hanley, Patricia Hansen, Harry Hansen, Meta Hanson, Kenneth O. (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Hanson, Pauline SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Ha, Harding, Antony Hards, Terence Hardy, Burwell M. (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Hardy, John Edward SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Hardy, John Edward (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Hardy, John Edward (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Hardy, John Edward (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Ha, Haridas, Thandassery Haring, Phyllis Harmon, Jack Harmsworth, Desmond Harney, John Paul Harper, Carol Ely (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Ha, Harper-Collins, R.S. Harrer, Irene J. Harrigan, Anthony (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Ha, Harris, Marguerite Harris, Robert Davis Hart, John Barkley (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - Hart, Lawrence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Hart, Richard L. (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Hartman, Geoffrey SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Ha, Hartman, Rose M. Hassmer, Warren (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Ha, Hatfield, Jerald E. Hatmaker, David Hay, John Hayford, James Hayman, Lee R. (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Ha, Hays, H.R. Hayter, Robin (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Hazard, Geoffrey (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Hazel, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Hazel, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Hazel, Robert (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Hazel, Robert (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Ha-He, Hazo, Samuel Heanue, James (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Hearst, James (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Hearst, James (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Hecht, Anthony (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Hecht, Roger (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Hecht, Roger (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - He, Heinemann, Katherine Heminway, David Mason Hemphill, George Hendrickson, John R. Hendry, J.F. Henkel, Gary (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Henley, Elizabeth SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 119, Folder 15)